- 嘿 我能问你个问题吗?  - 当然
- Hey, can I ask you a question?  - Sure.
从我认识你开始 这靶子就在了
You've had this dart board since I've known you,
但我从来没见你玩过飞镖
but I've never seen you play.
哦 我们玩过... 一次
Oh, uh, we played... once.
我把窗户砸破了
I broke a window.
什么窗户?
What window?
就是那边那扇
That one over there.
Leonard 投球奖券在哪儿?
Leonard, where are the Skee-Ball tickets?
什么投球奖券?
Skee-Ball tickets?
就是我们三年前去游戏机房玩的时候赢来的
Yeah, from when we went to the arcade three years ago?
我终于决定要换什么奖品了
I finally decided what prize I want.
快点
Hurry up.
如果我还留着
Uh, if I still have them,
估计就在废料箱里
they're probably in the junk box.
你想换什么?
Ooh, what are you gonna get?
不关你的事
None of your business.
但如果你一会儿看到我
But when you see me wearing a flower
在翻领上带了朵花儿
in my lapel later,
很欢迎你来嗅嗅香味
you are most welcome to sniff it.
好了... 给你
Yup, oh... here you go.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
给你 去换个橡皮擦玩吧
Here, get yourself an eraser for your troubles.
哦
Oh.
这个
Oh-ho.
我都忘了这个了
I forgot about this.
我考上大学的时候 我婶婶给我做的
My aunt made it for me when I started college.
她是不是讨厌你?
Aw, did she hate you?
为什么这么说? 就因为给了我一件扎人的丑毛衣
Why? Because I got an ugly, itchy sweater,
而给了我弟弟一辆车吗? 当然不 我是她最爱的孩子
and my brother got a car? No, I was her favorite.
好吧 好像还缺几张奖券
Yeah, I seem to be a few tickets short.
盒子里还有吗?
Are there more in the box?
我好像都拿出来了
Hmm, I think I got them all.
没了 里面没了
Nope, they're not in there.
你都没好好找 我来看看
Well, you barely looked. Let me see.
才不是 我... 我找了...
No, no, no, I... I looked, and...
没有奖券了
no more tickets.
Leonard 让我看看盒子里有什么
Leonard, let me look in the box.
好吧 好吧!
Okay, okay!
我会给你看盒子里的东西
I'm gonna show you what's in the box.
但你得保证... 别发疯
But just... promise not to flip out.
我干嘛要发疯?
Why would I flip out?
里面有蜘蛛吗?
Is it a spider?
真的有蜘蛛!
It's a spider!
不 如果真的有蜘蛛
No, if it was a spider,
Lenny肯定先疯了
Lenny would've flipped out.
好吧 Sheldon
Okay, Sheldon,
我知道我很早之前
I know I was supposed to return
就该去把这张碟还掉
this DVD a long time ago,
我也知道是用你的卡
and I know we rented it
租的
on your card.
但都已经过去快七年了
But it's been, like, seven years
也没发生什么坏事
and clearly nothing bad has happened.
所以... 与其和平时一样
So in... in... in... instead of being
你又叫又闹 使劲折腾
a giant pain in the ass like you always are,
能不能
what if
这次就试着冷静点呢?
this one time you just tried staying calm?
这要求好像挺合理的
That seems like a reasonable request.
但我还是得说 "嘿 Leonard 你能不能
Although so did, "Hey, Leonard, would you mind
把碟去还了?"
returning that DVD?"
对不起 我... 我会去还掉的
I'm sorry. I'll... I'll take care of it.
好吧
Okay.
我是说真的 真的会去还
I mean it, I'm going to.
我相信你
I believe you.
而你会继续保持冷静?
And you're going to stay calm?
我说过会的
I said I would.
怎么样?
How about that?
Sheldon讲道理了
Sheldon's being reasonable.
没错 我被吓到了
Yeah, it's freaking me out.
我还是走吧
I'm gonna go.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季第八集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见
校对：uu要A
所以... 你说
So... when you say
你不会为了影碟的事乱发疯
you're not going to freak out about the DVD,
应该包括以下几点
here's what that means.
别盯着这件事
Don't fixate on it.
别大半夜把我叫醒
Don't wake me up in the middle of the night.
别在我上厕所的时候
Or nag me through the door
隔着门教训我
while I'm on the toilet.
首先我得说清楚 你上厕所的时候和你说话
Okay, first, talking to you while you're on the toilet
我也不好受 好吗?
isn't exactly a picnic for me either, okay?
记得...
Remember...
你能听到我讲话 我也能听到你放屁
when you can hear me, I can hear you.
其次...
And second...
你完全忽略了
you completely disregard
未尽事宜让我很不舒服这一点
how uncomfortable unresolved issues are for me.
这... 这就像是...
It's... it's like, a...
大脑有点痒 我却挠不到
an itch in my brain I can't scratch.
我手臂骨折的时候
When I broke my arm I used
就那衣架插这儿挠痒
to stick a coat hanger down there.
你试过吗? 插耳朵里挠挠?
You ever try that? Maybe go in through the ear?
如果你明白我的感受 就不会开这种玩笑
You wouldn't make jokes if you could feel the way I feel.
我也没法明白你的感受
Well, I don't know how to do that.
这样如何?
How about this?
我保证不会为影碟的事纠缠你
I promise I won't pester you about the DVD.
上厕所也不会骚扰你
You can defecate in peace.
这是双赢
That's a win for both of us.
但是...
But...
在这件事解决之前
until this matter is resolved,
我要你
I would like you
穿着这毛衣
to wear this sweater.
里面还不准穿其它衣服
With nothing underneath it.
这太蠢了
That's stupid.
为什么?
Why?
你说了这毛衣穿着扎人 不舒服
You say it's itchy and uncomfortable.
在我看来 这件事给我的感受完全相同
I say situations like this make me feel the same way.
我跟你说了 试试看用衣架挠
I'm telling you, try the hanger.
穿上
Put it on.
我们来分享一下这感受
Let's share the experience.
好吧
You got it.
如果穿上这件毛衣就能让你闭嘴的话
If this sweater shuts you up,
大家都会来买的
I'm gonna make a fortune
那我就发财了
selling them to everyone we know.
至于现在...
Now...
我只需要
all I need to do
到楼下的光盘店
is head down to the video store
把影碟还回去就行了
and return the DVD.
哦 我是不是忘记告诉你了?
Oh, did I forget to tell you?
那家店好几年前就关门了
That store went out of business years ago.
真的?
Really?
你的咪咪感觉如何?
How those nipples feeling, chief?
Penny 能把我俩的饮料给我们不?
Penny, can we please get our drinks?
好啊 稍等一下
Yeah, hang on, just give me sec.
今天上班的时候 我做了活体立体定位手术
At work today, I did an in vivo stereotaxic surgery.
高端啊 今天我在实验室里
Cool. At my lab,
做了十次激光捕获微切割
I performed ten laser capture micro-dissections.
我今天从那张桌子底下扣下来了一块口香糖
I scraped gum off the bottom of that table.
就因为经理看见是我粘在那的
Only because my manager saw me put it there.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
她就是那个让Rajesh伤心欲绝的女孩
That's the girl that broke Rajesh's heart.
是Lucy?
That's Lucy?
我不知道为什么 但是我总把她想象成印度人
I don't know why but I always pictured her as Indian.
貌似这就叫种族歧视吧
I think that reason's called racism.
我要去跟她聊聊
I'm gonna go talk to her.
为什么? 你想说什么啊?
Why? What are you gonna say?
我不会乱说的
I'm not gonna say anything.
我就是想去见见她
I just want to check her out
因为她伤害了我朋友
because she hurt my friend.
我的印度朋友
My Indian friend.
现在是谁种族歧视?
Who's racist now?
你啊 因为你刚把他叫做你的
You because you just called him
"印度朋友"
your "Indian friend."
好吧 总之你长不高
Yeah, well, you're short.
我们再也喝不上饮料了
We're never getting our drinks.
反正也不抱期望
No, but we knew that.
嗨 想先喝点什么呢?
Hey, can I start you off with something to drink?
哦 水就行
Oh, water would be great.
好的
Okay.
呃 你是Lucy?
Um, you're Lucy, right?
我是Raj Koothrappali的朋友
I'm a friend of Raj Koothrappali's.
其实是Amy认出来的你
Actually Amy recognized you.
哇
Wow.
他现在怎么样?
How's he doing?
哦 你懂的啊 还好啦
Oh, you know, he's good.
那就好
Great.
其实 这事跟我没什么关系
Yeah, this is none of my business.
不过 你为什么要用发邮件的方式跟他分手?
But why did you break up with him in an e-mail?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.
可能就是觉得这样比较容易吧
I guess I thought it would be easier.
好吧 我懂了
Yeah, I get that.
我去给你拿杯水
I'll go get you your water.
你说"容易"的意思是
When you say "easier,"
这对于你来说更容易 对吧?
you mean easier for you, right?
因为显然对他来说这根本不容易
Because it certainly didn't make it easier for him.
我能不能
Any chance I can get
换个服务员?
a different waitress?
对... 对不起 是我不好
I... I'm sorry, this is rude of me.
我去给你拿水
I will go get that water.
你看 你看 你看
See, see, see, see.
就在刚才 你面对面地告诉我你的感受了
Just now you expressed your feelings to my face.
为什么你能这么面对我 却不能这么面对Raj?
How come you could do that with me, but not Raj?
因为我不知道你的邮箱啊
I don't know your e-mail.
你知道最糟糕的是什么吗?
You know what the worst part is?
你现在开开心心地坐在这里
You're sitting here, perfectly happy
他却窝在家里哭成一团
and he's at home, a blubbering mess.
哦 你刚才不是说他挺好的嘛
Oh, I thought you said he was okay.
是啊 我还说要给你拿水呢
Well, I also said I was getting you water,
我不还是站在这里么
but look at me still standing here.
知道吗 我可能不是个好服务员
You know, I may be a bad waitress,
但你根本就是个坏人
but you are a bad person.
现在 要听听今天的特价菜是什么吗?
Now, you want to hear the specials?
所以你永远不能脱下来?
So, you can never take it off?
不能
No.
睡觉的时候也不行?
Not even to sleep?
不行
No.
你简直就是个白痴
So, you're just an idiot?
这是在摆明立场
It's called proving a point.
那立场就是你是个白痴?
Is the point you're an idiot?
先生们 听我说
Gentlemen, please.
Leonard正在努力感同身受呢(直译为穿我的鞋)
Leonard is trying to walk a mile in my metaphorical shoes.
他穿不了我真实的鞋
He can't walk in my actual shoes.
他那脚只能穿童鞋呢
He has the feet of a toddler.
要是那家店已经停业了的话
So, how are you gonna return the DVD
你打算怎么还光盘?
if the store went out of business?
周一早上我要去趟市中心
Monday morning I'll go downtown
找找店主的信息
look up the owner's information.
然后把光盘寄给他
And send him the DVD.
再把罚款交了
Pay the late fee.
这样 我就可以向Sheldon证明
And prove to Sheldon
不用那么抓狂...
that you can have a problem and solve it...
也可以发现并解决问题了
without acting like a complete lunatic.
哈!
Ah!
扮狗熊的人还想让每个人都知道(指美国林务局的吉祥物Smokey熊)
And the man impersonating a bear would like everyone
"只有你能防止森林火灾"呢
to know that "Only you can prevent forest fires."
什么意思
I don't get it.
你们印度没有Smokey熊吗?
You didn't have Smokey the Bear in India?
没有 哦 他是不是和猫鼬萌萌差不多?
No. Oh, is he anything like, uh, Mun-Mun the Mongoose?
萌萌告诉我们不要招惹眼镜蛇
He taught us not to play with cobras.
不要招惹眼镜蛇还用人教?
You had to be taught not to play with cobras?
还有人教你们
You had to be taught
不能烧了森林呢 对吧?
not to burn down the forest?
嘿 你们要是饿了的话
Hey, if you guys were hungry, why didn't you order
为什么在餐厅的时候不要点吃的?
something at the restaurant?
我们要了 你一直没给我们啊
We did, you never brought it.
哦 想起来了
Oh, that's right.
是栗米脆饼和火鸡
Nachos and a turkey club.
差的也太远了吧
Not even close.
我是忙着给朋友出气
Well, I was too busy standing up
才忘了你们的...
for my friend to worry about your...
我想想该说什么
I want to say
是三文鱼吧
salmon.
还是说对不起吧
You want to say sorry.
你要怎么跟Raj说你干的好事?
So, how are you gonna tell Raj abut what you did?
什么叫"怎么说"? 这有什么大不了的?
What do you mean "how"? What's the big deal?
你跟Lucy说Raj现在可怜兮兮 生活一团糟
You told Lucy he was a pathetic mess.
后来你还把人家弄哭了 气走了
Then you made her cry and leave.
好啦 你们太小题大做了
Okay, you guys are overreacting.
我为Raj报了一箭之仇 他会感谢我的
Raj is gonna appreciate how I had his back.
你脑子被驴踢了吗 Penny?
What is wrong with you, Penny?!
我跟Lucy重修旧好的机会
You ruined any chance I had
都让你给毁了!
of getting back with Lucy!
现在她实实在在知道我是个惨兮兮的可怜虫啦
Now she knows I'm a desperate mess
以前她只不过是很肯定而已
instead of just being pretty sure!
是Lucy
It's Lucy.
她想约我喝咖啡
She wants to meet for coffee.
爱死你啦 Penny!
I love you, Penny!
嘿 在忙什么呢?
Hey, what're you working on?
我在想
I'm thinking about
高速旋转的镜子
how one could use the fact
能让假光子变成成真的光子
that a rapidly rotating mirror
那我们是否可以利用这种现象
turns virtual photons into real ones
来探索观察暗能量的方法呢
as a method of observing dark energy.
这想法很酷
That's a pretty cool idea.
耶 你来得正好
Yeah. It's great you're here.
我想听听工程师的看法
I'd love to get an engineer's opinion.
没问题
Sure.
这把椅子老是咯吱咯吱响
This chair is squeaky.
能修好吗? 不行我再换一把
Now, do I fix it or get a new one?
啊哈 Sheldon 我浪费了一早上的时间
Well, Sheldon, it took me all morning,
找到那家影碟店的老板了
but I found the owner of the video store.
但是 听好了 他已经死翘翘了 喝醉后安详地睡死过去了
And I am happy to report that he died peacefully in his sleep,
沉到了游泳池底部
drunk at the bottom of a pool.
总之就是 这张DVD还不回去了
Anyway, there is no one to return the DVD to,
所以 跟你的恩怨到此结束
so this issue is resolved.
哈...
Ah...
我还想说
And I'd just like to point out that
虽然这件毛衣快把我扎死了
even though the sweater was uncomfortable,
我也没有以此为借口
I didn't use it as an excuse
找身边任何人的茬儿
to antagonize everyone around me.
貌似你可以还给
You know, you could reimburse
影碟店老板的某个亲戚啊
the video store owner's next of kin.
我说了到此结束!
Or it's resolved!
嘿 Haward的主意听起来很不错哦
Hey, that next of kin thing sounds pretty good.
给你 不谢
This is yours.
问你俩一个问题
Can I ask you guys a question?
我明天晚上要见Lucy
So, I'm seeing Lucy tomorrow night,
我还从没跟已经跟我分手的人约会过
and I've never hung out with someone who broke up with me.
该怎么做呢
How do you do it?
别让她知道你被她伤害了
You can't let her know you're hurting.
关键是自信
You know, the key is confidence.
为什么关键总是自信?
Why is the key always confidence?
怎么从来都不是腰上的赘肉和紧张出来的汗呢?
How come it's never love handles and flop sweat?
这个女孩伤你那么深
If this girl hurt you so much,
你确定还想见她?
are you sure you want to see her again?
呃 容我插一句
Well, if I may...
他几乎没啥自尊
he has so little self-respect
又极其渴望
and is so desperate
哪怕是一星半点的关爱
for the smallest crumb of affection,
Lucy就算是跟他老爹滚床单
she could literally sleep with his own father
并且把视频传到YouTube上
in his own bed and post the video to YouTube,
这笨蛋还会给她买花
and he'd still buy her flowers
向她求婚呢
and ask her to be his bride.
没错
He's right.
但是 叫我说啊 是可忍
But in my defense, if we could survive that,
孰不可忍
we could survive anything.
好吧 既然你确定你想见她
Well, if you're sure you want to do this,
那就只是喝喝咖啡
it's only coffee...
心态放轻松 顺其自然吧
just relax and see what happens.
那 我能夸她漂亮不?
Well, can I say she looks nice?
当然
Sure.
我能告诉她我想她了吗？
Can I tell her I miss her?
看情况 要是她问的话
Maybe, if she asks.
哦 我能让她看看我画的一幅油画吗?
Oh, can I show her an oil painting I made
上面画着我俩儿孙绕膝
of us surrounded by our children and grandchildren?
还是下次约会再看吧
I'd save that for the second date.
好主意 好主意
Good, good.
我反复试了很多次
'Cause no matter how hard I try,
还是没能把那对双胞胎画得一样
I cannot get the twins to look alike.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
噢 我要找到那个傻叉老板的
Oh, I'm just trying to find the stupid next of kin
傻叉亲戚
to this stupid video store owner
这样我就可以归还那张影碟
so I can return the DVD
看到Sheldon脸上的傻叉表情了
and see the look on Sheldon's stupid face
我要让他知道 这点儿事哪能难倒我
when he sees that I didn't let this get to me.
Sheldon又不在这儿
Sheldon's not here.
为啥不把毛衣脱了呢?
Why don't you take the sweater off?
这-这-这是原则问题!
Th-Th-There's a principle at stake!
- 什么原则?  - 噢 不知道
- Which is?  - Oh, I don't know.
很重要吗? 看看我!
Who cares? Look at me!
噢 老天爷!
Oh, my God!
那是件毛衣 还是个蜂窝啊
Is that sweater made of bees?
快点 脱下来 我不会出卖你的
Come on, take it off. I won't tell.
不 不行 亲爱的 要是我脱了 Sheldon就赢了
No, no, honey, if I take it off, Sheldon wins.
亲
Sweetie...
每天晚上你没在他熟睡的时候杀了他
every night you don't kill him in his sleep,
就已经是他赢了
he wins.
哎呀 就-就快熬到头了
Nah, i-it's... it's almost done.
我 我只用找到
I just, I have to find...
他的亲戚 把影碟还回去
the next of kin, and send 'em the DVD
接下来就皱着个苦瓜脸等某人来
and then just wait for someone with my complexion to die
然后我就去做个制皮手术
so I can get a skin graft.
笑
Smile.
干啥-什么呀?
What-what is that?
拍我干啥?
What is that for?
发给普利斯顿大学
So you can send it to Princeton
把你交的学费要回来（这么笨 学都白上了）
and get your money back.
不得不说 Sheldon
I must say, Sheldon,
DVD这件事你处理得相当老练
you're handling this DVD business
叫人佩服呀
with an impressive amount of maturity.
真奇怪 这你都会觉得惊喜
I don't know why that surprises you.
我已经是个成年人了
I'm a grown man.
从我这身行头不也能看出来嘛
As should be evident by this sport coat
短外套 翻领上别一朵高仿花朵
and very real flower in my lapel.
你正在使用什么新的问题应对机制吗?
Is there some kind of new coping mechanism you're employing?
你更应该问
The more interesting question you should be asking is:
"这朵花什么味道?"
"What does this flower smell like?"
我猜是悲伤的味道
I'm gonna go with sad.
说说是怎么回事
So what's the story
你和这DVD到底怎么了?
with you and this DVD?
没什么
There's nothing to tell.
我买了一本书
Maybe I purchased a book entitled,
题目叫"不要为小事苦恼"
Don't Sweat the Small Stuff
它里面的建议挺不错的
and I followed its wise suggestions,
其中有一条:
one of which was:
停下来闻闻花香
stop and smell the flowers.
真的吗?
Seriously?
求你了
Please.
哈哈!
Ha-ha!
哦
Oh.
- 嗨  - 你好
- Hi.  - Hello.
见到你真高兴
Oh, it's so good to see you.
我也是
You, too.
请坐吧
Please, sit.
我给你点了一杯卡布奇诺
I, uh, I got you a cappuccino.
我记得这是你的最爱
I remembered it was your favorite.
哦 我还点了面包屑
Oh. I also got crumb cake,
但后来想起来这是我的最爱 所以我就把它吃了
but I remembered it was my favorite and I ate it.
好吧 你怎么样?
Anyway, uh, how are you?
还不错
I'm pretty good.
真是很抱歉
Listen, I just wanted to apologize
用电子邮件跟你分手
for breaking up with you in an e-mail.
我把面包屑全吃掉了
Well, and I ate all the crumb cake.
我们都有做的不好的地方嘛
We both made mistakes.
好吧
Okay.
你约我出来太让我高兴了
I'm so happy you asked me here,
希望以后我们也能常一起出来玩
and I hope we can hang out again sometime.
就像朋友那样
You know, as friends,
或是炮友神马的
lovemaking partners, whatever.
哦...
Oh, uh...
我已经有对象了
I'm kind of seeing someone.
我知道这显而易见
I think I know the answer to this,
不过还是想确认一下 你说的不是我 是吧?
but just to be clear, it's not me, right?
这都怪你!
This is all your fault!
我应该听萌萌的话
I should've listened to Mun-Mun
因为我竟然和眼镜蛇一起玩
because I've been playing with a cobra
她叫Penny!
and her name is Penny!
你怎么那么残忍?
Why are you so cruel?
看到我心碎你很开心吗?
Do you enjoy my pain?
起司蛋糕店有个女孩 我可以介绍给你认识
There's a girl at the Cheesecake Factory I can set you up with.
爱死你了 Penny!
I love you, Penny!
为什么我能解释清楚
How is it I can conceptualize a methodology
检测宇宙黑暗物质的方法论
of examining dark matter in the universe
却搞不明白怎么修好一朵喷水花?
but can't figure out how to fix a novelty squirt flower?
其实问题在于
I think the real question is,
你为什么要浪费时间修理这个小孩子的玩意儿?
why do you waste your time with cheap, childish pranks?
这是一个很深奥的问题
There's probably a deep reason.
我想一边品尝花生碎
Which I'd be happy to discuss with you
一边与你探讨
over some peanut brittle in a can.
好吧 Sheldon 我受够了!
Okay, Sheldon, I am out of options!
音像店老板Nursis Manookian
Video store owner, Nursis Manookian,
根本没有亲属!
has no next of kin!
你看起来有点热...
Well, you seem hot under the collar...
是因为毛衣吗?
or is that the sweater?
哦 不 不
Oh, oh, no, no.
是因为整个下午
It... It's because I spent all afternoon
都在亚美尼亚教堂参加他的葬礼
at the Armenian church where his funeral mass was held.
听Solakian神父说
According to Father Solakian,
没有别人会去
no one attended.
还好我没有白走一趟
Luckily, my trip wasn't a complete waste.
我点了根蜡烛 祈祷上帝快点把你带走
I lit a candle and prayed for your death.
但我不是亚美尼亚人 所以应该不灵验!
But I'm not Armenian, so it probably won't work!
这事结了 是吧?
This is over, right?
还不一定
Oh, not necessarily.
我建议
I suggest
你去亚米尼亚或是黎巴嫩
you look for long-lost relatives
寻一下亲
either in Armenia or Lebanon.
听着 Sheldon
Listen to me, Sheldon.
我不会去黎巴嫩
I am not going to Lebanon
只为还"超级玛丽兄弟"这部电影!
to return Super Mario Bros. the movie!
或许很有意思呢
You know, it might be fun.
你喜欢鹰嘴豆泥
You love hummus.
为什么你不烦恼?
Why isn't this bothering you?
难道你心里就不会不安吗?
It... Isn't your brain getting itchy?
这是用你的卡租的
This is on your card.
这会给你带来不良信用记录的!
This could be ruining your credit score!
你怎么能忍呢?
Why isn't this making you crazy?
Leonard 听着...
Leonard...
我要跟你说件事
I have something to tell you,
但你要答应我 别发疯
but I want you to promise not to flip out.
什么事?
What?
七年前
Seven years ago,
我发现这个DVD租期到了
I found out the DVD was late
于是就把它买了下来
and I paid for it.
再说一遍?
What?
我本来想告诉你的
I was going to mention it at the time,
但后来又想 有一天
but then I thought, some day,
可能这个能给某人一点教训
this might be a teachable moment.
啊...
Hah...
我... 你...
I... you...
怎么...
How can...
怎么?!
What?!
哦 Sheldon...
Sheldon...
这么做太坏了
that was diabolical.
我知道
I know.
太艰辛了
And it wasn't easy.
苦等了这么多年
Do you have any idea what it's like
只想看谁能笑到最后
to wait for years and never know
你知道这有多难熬吗?
who would finally get satisfaction?
哇
Wow.
你比Penny说的还漂亮
You're even prettier than Penny said.
难以置信
I can't believe
你这样的女孩竟然没有男朋友
a girl like you doesn't have a boyfriend.
确实没有
Well, I don't.
我才不信 你这个骗子!
I don't believe you, you're lying to me!
你说什么?
What?
哦 没什么
Oh, it's okay.
我已经寂寞得没有节操了
I have no morals and I'm desperately lonely.
如果你喜欢踏两只船
I'll be the other man
我也觉得无所谓啊
if you want a little something-something on the side.
你脑袋被驴踢了吧?!
What is wrong with you?!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见
校对：uu要A